const allQuestions = [
  {
    question: "NodeJS was written in?",
    answer: "C++",
    options: ["Javascript", "C++", "Java"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a forbidden curse?",
    answer: "Imperio",
    options: ["Imperio", "Stupefy", "Petrificus Totalus"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who killed Sirius Black?",
    answer: "Bellatrix Lestrange",
    options: ["Narcissa Malfoy", "Kingsley Shacklebolt", "Bellatrix Lestrange"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these is not a technique unleashed by the Mangekyo Sharingan?",
    answer: "Rasengan",
    options: ["Amaterasu", "Rasengan", "Susano'o"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a programming language?",
    answer: "React Hooks",
    options: ["Python", "React Hooks", "Squirrel"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a house at Hogwarts?",
    answer: "Bathilda Bagshot",
    options: ["Bathilda Bagshot", "Helga Hufflepuff", "Godric Gryffindor"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "One of the following players has won Fifa Balon d'Or with Multiple teams.",
    answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    options: ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Neymar"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these is not a quidditch player position in Harry Potter?",
    answer: "Defender",
    options: ["Beater", "Defender", "Seeker"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who else could lift Thor's hammer in Avengers.",
    answer: "Captain America",
    options: ["Captain America", "The Hulk", "Iron Man"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which one of the following is a CSS framework.",
    answer: "Bulma",
    options: ["Goku", "Contour CSS", "Bulma"],
  },
  {
    question: "The 'S' in 'HTTPS' stands for?.",
    answer: "Secure",
    options: ["Safe", "Secure", "Script"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Javascript is a multi-threaded language that can be none-blocking.",
    answer: "False",
    options: ["False", "True", "Don't know"],
  },
  {
    question: "Tim Berners-Lee is best know as the inventor of what?",
    answer: "World wide web",
    options: ["HTML", "Javascript", "World wide web"],
  },
  {
    question: "One of the below named is a co-founder of Nike.",
    answer: "Phil Knight",
    options: ["Duncan Unsworth", "Phil Knight", "Olivier Armstrong"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the beautiful actress that plays Wonder Woman?",
    answer: "Gal Gadot",
    options: ["Gal Gadot", "Emilia Clarke", "Jennifer Lawrence"],
  },

  //next 15 questions
  {
    question: "Who is the worlds richest man as of April 2020?",
    answer: "Jeff Bezos",
    options: ["Bill Gates", "Jeff Bezos", "Bernard Arnault"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is not an array method?",
    answer: "Split",
    options: ["Split", "Reverse", "Join"],
  },
  {
    question: "What team is the richest football club in England?",
    answer: "Manchester United",
    options: ["Liverpool", "Manchester City", "Manchester United"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who was Harry's first crush in Harry Potter",
    answer: "Cho Chang",
    options: ["Ginny Weasley", "Cho Chang", "Fleur Delacour"],
  },
  {
    question:
      "Select which of the following that is not a low-level programming language",
    answer: "Python",
    options: ["C++", "Python", "Java"],
  },
  {
    question: "The TV show The Big Bang Theory ran for how many seasons?",
    answer: "12",
    options: ["13", "12", "11"],
  },
  {
    question: "The COVID-19 pandemic broke out in what province in China?",
    answer: "Wuhan",
    options: ["Guangzhou", "Shanghai", "Wuhan"],
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the founder of Alibaba?",
    answer: "Jack Ma",
    options: ["Jack Ma", "Jeff Bezos", "Bill Gates"],
  },
  {
    question: "Steve Jobs is most famous for?",
    answer: "Apple",
    options: ["Samsung", "Apple", "Nokia"],
  },
  {
    question: "The name Meredith Grey is synonymous with what TV show?",
    answer: "Grey's Anatomy",
    options: ["Chicago Fire", "Grey's Anatomy", "Modern Family"],
  },
  {
    question: "Jim Parsons is best known the role of?",
    answer: "Sheldon Cooper",
    options: ["Harvey Specter", "Jackson Avery", "Sheldon Cooper"],
  },
];

export default allQuestions;
